I'M GRANTING 100 KIDS
THEIR BIGGEST WISH BECAUSE
FOR MOST OF YOU
WATCHING, YOUR CHILDHOOD PROBABLY
LOOKS SIMILAR TO MINE.
BUT KIDS LIKE MACK
SPENT THEIRS FIGHTING FOR
THEIR LIFE, HOWEVER, TO
CELEBRATE COMPLETING HIS CANCER
TREATMENT. AND IF YOU
COULD HAVE ONE WISH
FOR ANYTHING IN LIFE,
WHAT WOULD IT BE?
UGH,
AND WE'RE HERE! ALRIGHT,
LAST ONE DOWN FOR
OUR DAY!
THE DAY THAT WE
GOT THE DIAGNOSIS MACK
GRABBED MY HAND, HE
SAID, MOM, THIS MIGHT
BE HARD, BUT I'M
GONNA BE OKAY. YOU
DID IT!
AND THAT WAS JUST
THE FIRST OF 100
WISHES, NOT JUST I,
BUT ME WILL BE
GRANTING IN THIS VIDEO.
THE WORLD'S BIGGEST CREATORS,
CHART -TOPPING MUSICIANS, AWARD
-WINNING ACTORS, LEGENDARY ATHLETES
LIKE LEBRON JAMES.
YES, LEBRON JAMES IS
LITERALLY IN THIS VIDEO.
OH,
I'VE JOINED TOGETHER TO
MAKE THESE WISHES COME
TRUE. BUT FOR OUR
NEXT WISH, RIVER JUST
WANTED TO MEET ME,
BUT I WANTED TO
TAKE IT UP A
NOTCH. THAT BUTTON IS
HOT. WHEN YOU PRESS
IT, A MASSIVE EXPLOSION
WILL GO OFF. HOW
DOES THAT MAKE YOU
FEEL?
NERVOUS. YEAH.
ME TOO. SAME.
SUBSCRIBE.
AND BECAUSE THE MOST
POPULAR WISH IN THE
WORLD IS THE MOST
MAGICAL PLACE ON EARTH,
THAT'S 30 OF YOU
GET DIZZY WORLD TO
YOURSELF. ALRIGHT, YOU GUYS
READY TO GO RIDE
SOME RIDES?
IS THIS YOUR FIRST
TIME HERE?
AWW. IT'S GONNA BE
THE BEST DAY EVER.
NO LIE, EVERYONE, JUST
GO STRAIGHT ON THE
RIDE. IS THIS A
BAD TIME TO SAY
I HATE ROLLER COASTERS?
BUT OH!
WHOA!
COME ON, SOME OF
THEM WANTED TO RIDE
THEIR FAVORITE RIDES.
LET'S GO RIDE THE
CHARACTER.
OR MEET THEIR FAVORITE
CHARACTERS. A FEW.
JUST WANTED TO SEE
TARIQ GET TRAUMATIZED. GO
AHEAD, GO AHEAD, GO
AHEAD. ALRIGHT.
OKAY.
BETTER START A FUN.
BUT WE STILL GOT
A LOT MORE PEOPLE
TO MAKE HAPPY.
THE ROCKS,
SPEED, AND SO MANY
OTHERS ALL CAME TOGETHER
TO HELP MAKE THESE
WISHES COME TRUE. I'M
HERE IN A HOSPITAL.
I WANT TO KNOW
WHY ARE WISHES IMPORTANT?
WELL, THESE WISHES ARE
PART OF LIFE -SAVING
CURES. GIVING THEM A
CORE MEMORY THAT CAN
HELP PUSH THEM THROUGH.
AND THAT'S WHY WE'RE
DOING THIS VIDEO. ABSOLUTELY.
HELP THEM AND THEIR
FAMILY. FOR OUR NEXT
WISH, ADDISON WANTED TO
SWIM WITH A WHALE
SHARK. THEY'RE THE BIGGEST
FISH IN THE WORLD.
THAT THING? YEAH, THAT
ONE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THEY'RE
DOING THIS.